VOJTECH VRBKA

Senior Swift Developer

CONTACTS

London, UK
<u>vojtech@vrbka.me</u>
<u>http://vrbka.me</u>
https://linkedin.com/in/vrbka/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages

Swift (5y), Objective-C (3y), SQL(3y), PHP (3y), HTML(3y), JavaScript (2y), Java (1y), Python (1y), NodeJS (1y)

Technologies

Reactive functional programming, Redux,Reactive feedback, FP, OOP, TDD, BDD, Unit Tests, Integration tests, UI Tests, Snapshot tests, RESTful web services, Core Data, Debugging, Profiling

Integrated services and frameworks

Bitrise CI, Swiftlint, fastlane, Fabric (Crashlytics), Firebase, Optimizely, Mixpanel, Instabug, UXCam, Cocoapods, Carthage

Development software: Xcode, Git (with gitflow), Sketch

EDUCATION

2009 - 2014 - Master degree in CSTechnical University of Ostrava, Czech
Republic

2012 - 2013 - ERASMUS program (CS) University of Aveiro, Portugal

LANGUAGES

English (C2), Czech (Native), Portuguese (A2)

ABOUT ME

Senior Swift Developer with an MSc in Computer Science and nine years of experience in developing successful iOS apps for both start-ups and established organisations. I work well in small and big teams (30+ iOS developers) supporting apps with millions of users.

I write code that is clean and re-usable with the right architecture in mind, to create sleek and user-friendly solutions. I am proficient in managing and delivering full application lifecycle due to my extensive coding background and my continuous enthusiasm for new technologies.

Seeking an iOS Swift Developer opportunity in London.

EXPERIENCE

















Babylon Health

London 10/2019 - 03/2020

Senior Swift Developer (contract)

Babylon believes it is possible to put an accessible and affordable health service in the hands of every person on earth.

- Developed on the door authentication using Auth0
- Tech: ReactiveSwift, ReactiveFeedback, Redux, UI/Unit Tests

JustEat

London 05/2019 - 09/2019

Senior Swift Developer (contract)

JustEat is biggest take-away delivery platform in the UK and it's available in 13 more countries.

- JustEat app redesign, support with app release
- Tech: Unit/UI Tests, CI, Firebase, Optimizely

Karhoo

London 06/2018 - 03/2019

Senior Swift Developer (contract)

Karhoo is a taxi booking platform integrated with Taxi Fleets worldwide.

- Developed SDK for Karhoo partners and Karhoo Demo App using the SDK
- Tech: VIPER, MVP+C, CI, TDD, Framework development

Ostmodern Ltd.

London 04/2018 - 06/2018

Senior Swift Developer (contract)

Ostmodern is a digital agency specialising in video-centred apps and web.

- Worked on Olympic Channel and Formula 1
- Tech: FRP, VOD, UI Tests

<u>Fitzdares Ltd.</u>

London 10/2017 - 04/2018

Senior Swift Developer

Fitzdares is a private bookmaker for high rollers allowing users to place sport bets.

- Greenfield swift project that I led and took ownership of.
- Tech: MVVM, FRP, TDD, CI, API design

Firefly Exp. Ltd.

London 04/2015 – 09/2017

Senior Swift Developer

Firefly is a travelling App that enables users to plan and track every step of their trips and explore places of interest around them.

• Tech: FRP, MVVM, TDD, Custom animations, Core Location, Core data

2008 - 2015 London / Remote

iOS / Web Developer

I worked on many projects over the years, list of all companies and project's I worked on can be found on my Linkedin profile.